My friends called the police, they
questioned me.
Everyone stopped me.
Everyone cut off my contact.
Dursultan lives in a small, dark flat on
the outskirts of Istanbul.
She arrived in Turkey 12 years ago.
Bilka, come here.
Initially, she came to work and earn a
living to escape poverty in Turkmenistan.
But time passed.
Today, she can no longer return to her
country.
Dursultan began by publishing videos
against the
Turkmen regime.
She then took part in demonstrations in
the streets of Istanbul.
We don't want dictatorship
That's when she started to be targeted.
Like the day she was in the middle of a
video conference meeting with other
opponents.
What do you want?
They took my identity card.
They took my money.
If I take my old ID card, they will ask
for it.
The people who are afraid of you are the
ones who are afraid of you.
They are the ones who are afraid of you.
I think they shot the capital.
The cities are empty.
They are without people, without spirits.
to say these things in Turkmenistan.
Major NGOs such as Amnesty International
and Human Rights Watch ranked Turkmenistan
among the most repressive states in the
world.
It's impossible
to know the exact number of political
prisoners in Turkmen jails.
However, she regularly receives examples
of abuses committed against opponents.